 [
     {
       "id": 1,
       "question": "1. What is JavaScript?",
       "options": ["A programming language", "A markup language", "A database", "A design tool"],
       "answer": "A programming language"
     },
     {
      "id": 2,
       "question": "2. Which keyword is used to declare variables in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["var", "int", "string", "variable"],
       "answer": "var"
     },
     {
      "id": 3,
       "question": "3. Which method is used to display a message in the console?",
       "options": ["console.log()", "print()", "display()", "message()"],
       "answer": "console.log()"
     },
     {
      "id": 4,
       "question": "4. What is the result of the expression: '5' + 2 in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["52", "7", "NaN", "Error"],
       "answer": "52"
     },
     {
      "id": 5,
       "question": "5. Which operator is used for strict equality comparison in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["==", "===", "=", "!="],
       "answer": "==="
     },
     {
      "id": 6,
       "question": "6. does the 'typeof' operator return for 'null' in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["object", "null", "undefined", "string"],
       "answer": "object"
     },
     {
      "id": 7,
       "question": "7. What does the 'this' keyword refer to in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["The current function", "The global object", "The parent object", "The calling object"],
       "answer": "The calling object"
     },
     {
      "id": 8,
       "question": "8. Which function is used to convert a string to a number in JavaScript?",
       "options": ["parseInt()", "toString()", "parseFloat()", "number()"],
       "answer": "parseInt()"
     },
     {
      "id": 9,
       "question": "9. What is the correct way to write a JavaScript comment?",
       "options": ["// This is a comment", "<!-- This is a comment -->", "' This is a comment", "/* This is a comment */"],
       "answer": "// This is a comment"
     },
     {
      "id": 10,
       "question": "10. Which event is triggered when a user clicks on an HTML element?",
       "options": ["onmouseover", "onchange", "onclick", "onsubmit"],
       "answer": "onclick"
     }
   ]
 
 